export default data = [
  {
      question: "In the keen competition of this international tennis tournament, she ______  won the championship.",
      options: ["privately","distantly","locally","narrowly"],
      correct_option: "narrowly"
  },
  {
      question: "This company, with its serious financial problems, is no longer ______ .",
      options: ["achievable","stretchable","repeatable","manageable"],
      correct_option: "manageable"
  },
  {
      question: "Your desk is crowded with too many unnecessary things. You have to ______ some of them.",
      options: ["remain","resist","remove","renew"],
      correct_option: "remove"
  },
  {
      question: "Most businessmen are more interested in the ______ success of their products than their educational values.",
      options: ["cultural","commercial","classical","criminal"],
      correct_option: "commercial"
  },
  {
      question: "The postal special ______ service is very efficient. A package sent can be received in a couple of hours.",
      options: ["delivery","directory","discovery","dormitory"],
      correct_option: "delivery"
  },
  {
      question: "Children don’t learn their native languages ______ , but they become fluent in them within a few years.",
      options: ["previously","variously","consciously","enviously"],
      correct_option: "consciously"
  },
  {
      question: "______ to what you think, our TV program has been enjoyed by a large audience.",
      options: ["Intensive","Contrary","Fortunate","Objective"],
      correct_option: "Contrary"
  },
  {
      question: "There is a ______ to one’s capacity; one should not make oneself overtired.",
      options: ["relaxation","contribution","hesitation","limitation"],
      correct_option: "limitation"
  },
  {
      question: "It is necessary for you to ______ this point. We simply cannot understand it.",
      options: ["clarify","falsify","purify","notify"],
      correct_option: "clarify"
  },
  {
      question: "Our team will certainly win this baseball game, because all the players are highly         .",
      options: ["illustrated","estimated","motivated","dominated"],
      correct_option: "motivated"
  },
  {
      question: "This story, ______ , is very fascinating: there are many interesting characters in it.",
      options: ["on the whole","under no circumstances","in no time","out of the question"],
      correct_option: "on the whole"
  },
  {
      question: "Most of our classmates are ______ taking a trip to Kenting National Park.",
      options: ["in honor of","in favor of","in search of","in place of"],
      correct_option: "in favor of"
  },
  {
      question: "We haven’t seen John for a long time. As a matter of fact, we have ______ him.",
      options: ["made up for","run out of","come to pass","lost track of"],
      correct_option: "lost track of"
  },
  {
      question: "Recently in Taiwan, the manufacturing industry has ______ the information industry.",
      options: ["found a way of","changed the way of","given way to","had a way of"],
      correct_option: "given way to"
  },
  {
      question: "His behavior at the party last night seemed rather ______ . Many of us were quite surprised.",
      options: ["out of practice","out of place","out of politeness","out of pity"],
      correct_option: "out of place"
  },
]
